恭喜了  老妈
Congratulations, mom.
噢  谢谢了  宝贝
Oh, thank you, sweetheart.
不敢相信你们这帮孩子还没忘
I was wondering if you kids would remember.
那是  谁能忘了像今天这样的日子
Well, who could forget a day like this?
有谁知道今天是什么日子吗
Any idea what we're talking about?
是我们二十周年结婚纪念日
It's our 20th wedding anniversary.
哇  和老爸一起熬了二十年
Wow, 20 years with dad.
哇  真是一位冷场高手
Wow, that's a real conversation stopper, isn't it?
好了  孩子们  你爸和我共度了二十年的美好时光
Okay, kids, your dad and I have had 20 wonderful years.
你爸这二十年也不容易  我是说  想想看
I gotta give the guy credit. I mean, let's face it...
有些时候我也不是省油的灯
Sometimes I may not be the easiest person in the world to live with.
现在你们应该插句话
This is where you all jump in.
说“别这么说  老妈  你是省油的灯”
And say, "no no no, mom. You're great."
别这么说  老妈  你是省油的灯
No no no, mom. You're great.
那老爸准备给你礼物吗
So is dad gonna get you a nice gift?
孩子们  我深爱着你们的老爸
Kids, I love your father dearly,
但是每当送周年礼物的时候
But when it comes to anniversary gifts,
就可以用一个词来形容
There's only one word to describe him.
第一个字是“便”  然后是“宜”
It starts with "ch" and ends in "eap."
能不能再给点提示
Yeah, I'm gonna need more hints.
曾经给过我的唯一礼物就是一张卡片  写着
Yeah, the only gift he ever gets me is a card he signs,
“周年快乐  爱你的  我”
"happy anniversary. Love, me."
知足吧  至少你还有卡片
Well, at least you get a card.
是同一张卡片  他每年都重复使用
It's the same card. He reuses it every year.
谁知道呢  也许今年他就惊喜你一下
Well, who knows? Maybe this year he'll surprise you.
是啊  也许他进厨房时能把拉链拉上
Yeah, maybe he'll come into the kitchen with his zipper up.
-大家  早上好  -老爸  文明扣开了
-Good morning, everybody. -Dad, barn door.
给你的  亲爱的
For you, my dear.
一张卡片
A card!
我很好奇上面写的什么
Wonder what it says.
“周年快乐  爱你的  我”
"happy anniversary. Love, me."
-我也爱你  -倍感荣幸
-I love you too. -Glad to hear it.
既然这样  继续读  今年有惊喜
In that case, read on. There's more this year.
"附  阿罗哈"  搞什么名堂
"P.S. Aloha." what does that mean?
(注：Aloha是夏威夷的问候语）
名堂就是咱们全家
That means that the Duncans.
要去夏威夷度假
Are going to Hawaii!
我就知道你不会让我失望的  你太慷慨大方了
I knew you'd come through. You are so generous.
噢  谢谢了  但我还要把这卡片收回
Oh, thank you. I'm gonna need that back.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
校订： line
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  liloelva
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第十八集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E18  Sun Show, Part.1
鲍勃  这地方太漂亮了
Bob, this place is gorgeous.
是吗  极品配佳人  亲爱的
Huh? Only the best for you, my love.
-噢  -好了  我去登记入住了
-Oh. -Okay, I'm gonna check us in.
好的
Okay.
-嘿  查莉  想去泳池玩吗  -好
-Hey, Charlie, you wanna find a pool? -Yeah
先确认下没有人和老娘我的泳装撞衫
Let's make sure no one has the same swimsuit as mommy.
好了  小伙子们  你们不用等我
Okay, guys, come on, you don't have to wait for me.
去外面转转  这里可是人间天堂啊
Go outside, explore. We're in paradise.
老哥  快看那块儿液晶屏有多大
Dude, look at the size of that flat-screen.
泰迪  你也不用和我一起
Teddy, you don't have to hang with me.
去吧  这里肯定也有你感兴趣的
Come on, there's got to be to check out too.
算了  没事的  我
No, that's okay. I...
找到了
Found it.
-嗨  呃  我叫泰迪  -你好  泰迪  我叫卡伊
-Hi, um, I'm Teddy. -Aloha, Teddy. I'm kai.
卡伊  好有意思的名字
Kai... what an interesting name.
意思是“大海”  “泰迪”的意思是什么
It means "the sea." what does "teddy" mean?
噢  意思就是我父母本想生个男孩
Oh, it means my parents were expecting a boy.
那你喜欢冲浪吗
So are you into surfing?
喜欢吗  我一直抱怨
Am I? I have been complaining about.
丹佛没有海浪  自从  我也不知道什么时候
The lack of surf in Denver since I don't know when.
如果你想学冲浪  那我明天早上在海滩等你
If you want a surfing lesson, I'll be at the beach tomorrow morning.
好啊  我想学
Yeah, I'd love that.
那好  阿罗哈
Okay well, aloha.
意思是“你好  再见  我喜欢你的微笑”
That means "hello, goodbye and I like your smile."
其实只有前两个的意思
Actually just the first two.
是啊  我知道  我只是想幽默下
Yeah. No, I know. I was going for an alo-ha-ha.
我还是走吧
I'm leaving now.
嗨  我想登记入住  我叫鲍勃·邓肯
Hi, I'd like to check in. The name is Bob Duncan.
我们有一份炎炎夏日礼包
I believe we have the sizzlin' summer package.
没错  这里  一间房
Yes, here it is... one room,
而且你还要分时间段入住
And I see you will be attending the timeshare presentation.
-嘿  -嘿  你都听到了什么
-Hey. -Hey! How much did you hear?
噢  没什么  就听见分时间段什么的  什么情况
Oh, not much, just something about a timeshare. What is that?
就是  你知道吗
It's... you know what it is?
这个很复杂  为什么不
It's complicated. Why don't...
分时段入住就是在你这一生中可以每年
Timeshare is a hotel room you buy one week every year.
-在这个酒店里住一周  -好了  她没有
-For the rest of your life. -Okay, she doesn't...
只要参加我们这个分时入住座谈会
For attending our presentation,
邓肯先生将免费获得此次旅行
Mr. Duncan gets his entire trip for free.
必要知道那些
... Need to know all that.
看来
So...
你送给老妈的周年礼物就是免费旅游
Your big anniversary gift to mom is a free trip?
这是双赢
This is a win-win.
你老妈认为我伟大了  而且我
Your mom thinks I'm a hero and I've got...
分时段入住也是我的无心之举
I've got no intention of buying a timeshare.
拜托了
<i>Come on.</i>
替我保密可以吗
Can't we keep this between us?
保密什么
Keep what between us?
我最欣赏你这点
That's why you're my favorite.
是啊
Yeah.
这就是我们的房间了
And here's our room!
我好喜欢
I love it!
噢  挺不错的  我们的房间在哪
Oh, this is sweet. Where's our room?
呃  出了些电脑故障  他们把我们的预约搞错了
Uh, it's a computer glitch. They messed up our reservation.
我觉着挺可信
Sounds believable to me.
等等  难道我们要挤在一间屋子里
Wait, we're all staying in one room?
噢  别这样  伙计们  这也不错啊  看看这个
Oh come on, you guys, this is gonna be great. Look at this...
我们甚至还能看到
We even have a view of what appears to be.
高尔夫停车场
The parking lot of a golf course.
我可不想与你们共处一室
I don't want to share a room with you people.
好了  你俩消停点儿  你们慷慨大方的父亲
Okay, you two stop it. Your very generous father.
花巨资把我们带到这里
Spent a lot of money to get us here.
听着也很可信
Sounds believable too.
那我们在哪睡觉
Where are we all gonna sleep?
简单  女生一张床上  男生睡另一张
It's simple... girls in one bed, guys in the other.
噢  不公平  我们有老爸
Oh, that is not fair. We have dad.
没错  但是查莉睡觉不老实
Yeah, but Charlie is a very restless sleeper.
但我们有老爸
But we have dad.
淡定  我们可以解决这个问题
Would you relax? We're gonna make this work.
嘿  查莉  我们现在在夏威夷
Hey, Charlie, here we are in Hawaii.
我在我床上  妈妈在我床上
I'm in my bed; Mom's in my bed;
你也在我床上
You're in my bed.
但是我们还不算最悲剧的  因为
But we still have the good bed because...
老爸  你能过去一点吗
Dad, can you scoot over?
-抱歉  -啊
-Sorry. -Ah!
好多了
That's better.
祝他们好运吧  查莉
Wish them good luck, Charlie.
感觉还不是很糟吗
That wasn't so bad.
你感觉倒是不错
Speak for yourself.
如果查莉·邓肯可以打进
If Charlie Duncan sinks this putt,
她将赢得到神童俱乐部的免费旅行
She wins a free trip to the kahuna kiddies' club.
届时妈妈也可以享受一下全身按摩
While mommy gets a full-body massage.
总之她还是赢得了这次旅行
And she wins the trip anyway!
-抱歉  你不能进去  -为什么
-I'm sorry, you can't go in there. -Why not?
-因为它是卡普的  -卡普
-Because it is <i>kapu.</i> <i>-</i> <i>Kapu?</i>
意思是“禁止”  那是一块圣地
It means "forbidden." that is sacred ground.
圣地  挨着浴巾小屋吗
Sacred ground? Next to the towel hut?
别忽悠我了
I don't think so.
停下  如果你进去了
Stop! If you go in there,
将有坏事发生
Bad things will happen.
听着  老兄  我有四个孩子
Listen, buddy, I have four kids.
而且我嫁给了一个灭虫专家
And I'm married to an exterminator.
这就是卡普带给我的
That's about as <i>kapu</i> as it gets.
-你搞什么  -给你施诅咒
-What are you doing? -Putting a curse on you.
噢  是吗
Oh really?
如果我被诅咒了  那我还能这样吗
Well, if I were cursed, could I do this?
现在你们全家都被诅咒了
Now your whole family is cursed.
噢  我们全家
Ooh, my whole family!
你们还有宠物吗  因为我们全天都可以这么干
Got any pets? 'cause we could do this all day.
我告诉你  你尽管诅咒好了
I'll tell you what... you do this all day.
我去享受我的假期了
And I'm gonna enjoy my vacation.
啊  在这里呢  哈哈  还诅咒我
Ah, there it is. Ha, cursed.
切
Plea...
我用的是速效诅咒
I used the fast-acting curse.
同志们  起来了  我们在夏威夷呢
Guys, come on. We're in Hawaii.
你们不能整天闷在屋子里玩电子游戏
You can't sit in a room all day playing video games.
只要你别管我们  我们就可以
We could if you'd leave us alone.
到底有什么好玩的
What could you possibly be playing.
能比得上在夏威夷度假
That could be better than exploring Hawaii?
这个好玩的游戏叫做“热带直升机大作战”
It's a really cool game called "tropical chopper challenge."
没错  现在我们正驾驶直升机飞越火山
Yeah, right now we're flying helicopters over volcanoes.
你也可以在现实中体验一下
You can do that for real on the island.
没错  但是画面有这个好吗
Yeah, but are the graphics this good?
-让我看看  -给
-Let's see. -Check it out.
噢  好耶
Oh! Oh yeah.
起来了  同志们  出发吧
Come on, guys, let's go.
来吧  我把你们送到直升机那里
Come on, I'm gonna drop you off at the helicopter.
这次经历会让你们永生难忘
You're gonna have the time of your lives.
看这个  我还有赠券呢
Look at this... I even got a coupon.
“哈尔折扣直升机
"hal's discount helicopter:
二月起开始为您服务”
Serving the island since February."
出发吧
Let's go.
嘿  盖比  在车里想玩“浮潜大冒险”吗
Hey, Gabe, in the car do you want to play "snorkeling adventure"?
除非夏威夷也有这东西
Unless they have that in Hawaii too.
嗨  卡伊  噢  还挺押韵
Hi, kai. Oh, that rhymed.
难道就我一个人吗
So am I the only one here?
是一对一教学吗
Is this gonna be a private lesson?
除非有别人的话  我去给你拿个冲浪板
Unless someone else shows up. Let me get you a board.
好的  一会见  鳄鱼宴
All right. Later, gator!
有点儿过了
Too much.
这里是有个冲浪课吗
Is this where the surfing lessons are?
呃  是啊  你对冲浪感兴趣
Uh, yeah. You're interested in surfing?
我在家喜欢电视冲浪
Well, at home I love channel surfing,
所以我想试试其他的冲浪
So I thought I'd try the other kind.
其实  你上这课应该有些困难
Well, you might have a hard time with this class.
老师不会说英语
The teacher doesn't speak any English whatsoever.
我马上回去  泰迪
I'll be right with you, Teddy.
哇  有进步了
Wow, he's gotten better.
那就是冲浪教练吗
<i>Is that the surfing</i> <i>instructor?</i>
-是的  -你想和他独处吗
-Uh-huh. -And you want to be alone with him?
是的  -那你干嘛不直说
-Uh-huh. -Why didn't you just say so?
夏威夷就是个浪漫之岛
Hawaii is for romance.
那我就再去换个地方来躲避我老公
I'll find somewhere else to avoid my husband.
谢谢
Thank you.
-再见  -再见
-Bye. -Bye.
-那是谁  -不清楚
-Who was that? -I don't know.
她不会说英语
She didn't speak any English.
噢  邓肯先生  提醒你一下
Oh, Mr. Duncan? Just want to remind you.
分段入住座谈会将于今天的三点开始
The timeshare presentation is today at 3:00.
好的  好的  顺便问一下  这次的座谈会多长时间
Yes yes. By the way, how long is the presentation?
六个半小时
6 and a half hours
哇  哇
Wo... wow.
为什么这么长
Why... why so long?
击垮人们的意志是需要一定时间的
It takes a while to break people down.
我是说  需要讲的内容有很多
I mean, we have a lot of ground to cover.
那好吧  再见
Okay. See you then...
也许不见
Or not.
-嘿  亲爱的  -嘿
-Hey, honey. -Hey.
-那是谁  -呃  他吗
-Who was that? -Uh, him?
呃  乒乓球服务主管
Uh... Director of ping-pong services.
想去游泳吗
Do you want to meet me by the pool?
好的  好的  我去拿泳衣  然后我给你讲讲诅咒的故事
Yeah yeah, let me grab my suit. And then I'll tell you about my curse.
讲什么
Your what?
一个有趣的故事  你就等着笑吧
Cute story. You're gonna laugh.
好吧
All right.
噢  真高兴你来了
Oh, I am so glad you're here.
谢谢  咱们认识吗
Thank you. Do I know you?
我只是非常害怕坐电梯
I happen to have a deathly fear of elevators.
我讨厌一个人乘坐它
I hate riding in them alone.
那好吧  现在你有一个电梯伙伴了
Well, now you have an elevator buddy.
-你还好吧  -目前还好
-You okay? -Fine so far.
相信我  如果这东西出故障了
But believe me, if this thing ever broke down,
你绝对不想和我关在这里
You would not want to be in here with me.
别担心  不会有事情发生的
Don't worry, nothing's going to happen.
-什么情况  -我们停下了
-What's going on? -We stopped.
你对我撒谎
You lied to me!
什
Wha...
别  别  冷静  我保证马上就会继续运行了
No no no, calm down. I'm sure we'll start up again in a second.
-啊  抱住我  -噢
-Ah, hold me! -Oh!
呃  好了  让我们试试紧急电话来求救某人
Um, okay, why don't we use the emergency phone to call someone?
好吗  我们一起走
Okay? Okay, we'll go together.
预备  走
Ready? Go.
很好  听着  放松一下  只要不停电
Okay, look, just relax. We're going to be fine.
我们就没事
As long as we don't lose power.
这是你们第一次坐直升机是吗  孩子们
First time in a helicopter, boys?
-是啊  -我也是
-Yep. -Mine too.
哈哈  一个直升机小笑话
Ha! A little helicopter humor.
嘿  那边是什么
Hey, what's that over there?
不知道  我只管往那里飞
No idea. Just moved here.
我带着旅客飞越大峡谷已经三十年了
Flew tours over the grand canyon for 30 years.
那座火山叫什么
What's the name of that volcano?
我也不知道
Beats me.
但是你知道那座大峡谷有一英里深吗
But did you know that the grand canyon's also a mile deep?
是吗  我不知道  但是现在学校放假
Yeah, I didn't, but school's out.
所以我不用学习新知识了
So I'm not supposed to be learning anything new.
关于夏威夷你都知道些什么
Do you know anything about Hawaii?
我知道他们有一些奇怪的食物
I know they got some weird food.
今天我吃了些怪异的鱼
I had some crazy fish today.
所以我现在有点儿坐不住了
It's not sitting too well.
你们两个谁知道如何开飞机吗
Either of you guys know how to fly one of these things?
噢  又是直升机小笑话
Oh, is that more helicopter humor?
这个不是笑话  我觉着我就要
Afraid not. I feel like I'm gonna...
-PJ  做点儿什么  -我在做
-P.J., do something. -I am.
醒醒  大叔  醒醒
Wake up, old dude! Wake up!
PJ  我们怎么办
P.J., what are we going to do?
说话啊  PJ  说话啊
Words, P.J.! Words!
噢
Oh.
这  也许我能驾驶这东西
Well, maybe I could fly this thing.
这些控制仪器有点儿像电子游戏里的
These controls kind of look like my video game.
但是僵尸大炮在哪呢
Where the heck is the zombie cannon?
老天爷啊  如果你能让我活下去
Please, God, if you let me live through this,
我向你保证我以后一定会行善积德的
I promise I'll do something good.
其实也可以骑驴来观赏大峡谷
Another way to see the grand canyon is by burro.
哇  你办事效率还挺高啊
Wow, you work fast.
好了  很好  稳住
All right, good, steady.
学会了吗  我能放手了吗
Think you got it now? Can I let go?
不  不能  为时尚早
No no, not quite yet.
好吧  我觉着平衡问题已经练得差不多了
Okay, so I think we've done enough balance.
现在练练冲浪板的控制如何
How about some board control?
噢  冲浪啊  冲浪
Oh, surfing surfing surfing.
这不就是我们的目的吗
That is why we're here, right?
是啊  但是我认为咱们应该先互相了解下对方
Yeah, but I thought maybe we could get to know each other.
好吧  我先来
Okay, I'll go first.
我喜欢沙冰
I love smoothies,
你是知道的  特别是在运动之后
Um, you know, especially after a workout.
或者在上完什么课之后
Or... or like a lesson of some kind.
那好  上完课后
Well, after the lesson's done,
想来杯沙冰吗
Do you want to get a smoothie?
看看你  总是想的比我快一步
Look at you... always one step ahead of me.
好了  你自己认为可以下水了吗
Okay, you think you're ready to hit the water?
可以了吧
I guess.
别担心  你很有天赋
Don't worry, you'll be a natural.
好的
Okay.
呜  太爽了
Whoo hoo! This is awesome!
呜  耶
Whoa yeah!
我说过你很有天赋的
I told you you'd be a natural.
噢  看着  金鸡独立
Oh, look, one foot.
噢  看着  飞龙在天
Oh, look, no feet.
犀利
Gnarly!
大家好
Cowabunga!
（注：Cowabunga是冲浪专用问候语）
嘿  你来干什么
Hey, what are you doing here?
这是我的私人课程
This is my private lesson.
你知道自己在做梦呢  是吧
You know you're dreaming, right?
什么
What?
快醒醒  泰迪
Wake up, Teddy!
泰迪  醒醒
Teddy, wake up.
宝贝  还好吧
Honey, you okay?
怎么回事
What happened?
我所记着的最后一件事就是我在上冲浪课
The last thing I remember I was at my surfing lesson.
没错  但是  课上的不怎么顺利
Yeah. Well, uh, that didn't go too well.
当第一波浪袭来时  你喊了句“我天赋异禀”
On your first wave, you shouted, "I'm a natural!"
然后你就来了个倒栽葱
And then you landed on your head.
噢  惨了
Oh no.
我居然错过了沙冰之约
I missed my smoothie date.
他那么迷人
He was so cute.
你又怎么了
What happened to you?
我快被我的电梯伙伴给折磨死了
I was almost smothered by my elevator buddy.
是吗  有啥大不了的  我们差点死于直升机坠毁
Oh yeah, big whoop. We were almost killed in a helicopter crash.
你没听见我说的吗  我错过了沙冰之约
Didn't you hear me? I missed my smoothie date.
哇  邓肯家的倒霉日啊
Wow, bad day for the Duncans.
就像整个家都被诅咒了
It's almost like the whole family's cursed.
你们看我干吗
What are you all looking at me for?
看什么  关于诅咒这事我什么也不知道
Huh? I... I don't know anything about a curse.
你早些时候不是提到过诅咒什么的吗
Didn't you mention something about a curse earlier?
没  没  没  没有
No no no. No no.
我记着我提到的是钱包
I think I might have mentioned something about a purse.
我为什么要提到诅咒啊
Why would I mention something about a curse?
你看  你和查莉就没有厄运缠身啊
I mean, nothing's happened to Charlie or you.
实话  我没事
That's true. I'm good.
闪开
<i>Fore!</i>
邓肯先生
Mr. Duncan?
嗨
Hi.
呃  我在  我在做一个植物快速检查
Um, I was just doing... just doing a quick plant inspection.
没错  这是一棵榕属
Yeah, that's a... that's a ficus.
您昨天没有参加分时入住座谈会
We missed you yesterday at the timeshare presentation.
如果您今天还没有参加
If you don't attend the one today,
我们将强迫让您缴纳这次旅行的所有费用
We'll be forced to charge you for your entire trip.
-所有费用  -甚至是夏威夷果
-Everything? -Down to the last macadamia nut.
你也是分时入住
Timeshare?
-嘿  -嘿
-Hey. -Hey.
盯着电视看  但电视是关着的
You're watching tv, but it's not on.
我不配任何娱乐活动
I don't deserve entertainment.
老哥  你怎么了
Dude, what's the matter with you?
直升机的那些经历  在我的脑海中挥之不去
I can't get what happened in the helicopter out of my head.
我感觉我是个懦夫
I just feel like a coward.
通常我的确会这么说  因为你就是个懦夫
Well, normally I'd say that's because you are a coward,
但是我发誓要行善积德  所以我不会再落井下石了
But I made this promise to be good, so I won't say that.
当那个直升机飞行员晕过去后  我就
When the helicopter pilot passed out, I just...
我就傻了
I froze.
我没有任何行动
I didn't do anything.
除了叫的像个女生
Except scream like a little girl...
剩下的我就不说了
Is something else I won't say.
感觉到了吗  好像你说的也不少
You know, it almost feels like you are saying those things.
我还不善于做个好人  肯定会有些不尽人意
Being good is new to me, so there's gonna be some snags.
我就像个废物
I just feel like a total loser.
等一下
Well, wait a minute.
我向老天爷保证我会行善积德
I made a promise to God to do something good.
如果我帮你正视你的恐惧  也算行善积德了
And if I help you face your fears, that would count, right?
那我就和老天爷两清了
And then God and I would be square.
-你愿意帮我  -这正是好人该做的
-You'd do that for me? -That's what good people do, right?
我是说  我也就能想到这里了
I mean, I'm just guessing here.
嘿  电梯伙伴
Hey, elevator buddy.
噢  亲爱的  你怎么了
Oh, dear, what happened to you?
游泳  遇到了水母  厄运缠身啊
Swimming... jellyfish. Things keep happening.
跟我来  查莉
Come on, Charlie,
咱们去花园转转
Let's go see the pretty garden...
或者去帅哥那里转转
Or let's go see the pretty boy.
花园又跑不了
The garden's not going anywhere.
-卡伊  -泰迪
-<i>Kai.</i> <i>-Teddy.</i>
你感觉怎么样了  昨天你摔得不轻
How are you feeling? That was quite the fall you took yesterday.
噢  没事了  我很好
Oh yeah, but I'm fine now.
咱们能再定下去喝沙冰的时间吗
So can we reschedule that smoothie?
等一下  让我查一下
Hold on, let me check.
我的冲浪课之后怎么样  可以吗
How about after my next surf lesson? Wanna meet then?
当然  没问题
Sure, I'd love that.
-那我们就约好了  -第二次是最好的
-Then it's a date. -Second time's the charm.
好了  进展得不错  查莉
Well, that went well, didn't it, Charlie?
查莉
Charlie?
Charlie!
未完待续